let questions=[ //Desktop
{ numb : 1,
question:"Which of the five choices is NOT a violation of the CJCP Computer School Internet Safety and Acceptable Use Policy for Information Technology Resources?",
answer:"Checking your personal e-mail during downtime in class.",
options:[
"Student distribution of private Information about themselves or others.",
"Transmission of spam, chain letters or other solicited mailings.",
"Checking your personal e-mail during downtime in class.",
"Cyber Bullying"
]
},
{ numb :2 ,
question:"Sometimes called the Central Processing Unit (CPU) or microprocessor, this chip performs all the calculations for the computer.",
answer:"Processor",
options:[
"Memory",
"Processor",
"Power Supply",
"none"
]
},
{ numb : 3,
question:"Microsoft has 5 programs that assist in making everyday tasks easier . The Microsoft Office Suite of applications can also be referred to as:",
answer:" Productivity Software",
options:[
"Specifications ",
"Productivity Software   ",
"Icons  ",
"Functions"
]
},
{ numb :4 ,
question:"photographic/digital images displayed on the internet is the:",
answer:"JPEG( Joint Photographic Experts Group)",
options:[
"JPEG( Joint Photographic Experts Group)",
"GIF( Graphical Interchange Format)",
"PNG(Portable Network Graphics)",
"none"
]
},
{ numb :5 ,
question:"Microsoft Word is a____________ Application.",
answer:"Word Processing",
options:[
"Word Processing",
"database",
"spreadsheet",
"none"
]
},
{ numb : 6,
question:"Microsoft Powerpoint is a____________ Application",
answer:"Presentation Software",
options:[
"Presentation Software",
"Word Processing",
"database",
"none"
]
},
{ numb :7 ,
question:"Microsoft Excel is a____________ Application.",
answer:"All of the above",
options:[
"database",
"spreadsheet",
"workbook",
"All of the above"
]
},
{ numb :8 ,
question:"An Internet facility that links documents locally and remotely.",
answer:"World Wide Web",
options:[
"World Wide Web",
"Internet",
"Website",
"Google"
]
},
{ numb :9 ,
question:"Software that creates professional looking documents is referred to as:",
answer:"Publishing Software",
options:[
"Word processing",
"Publishing Software",
"Typing programs",
"Operation system"
]
},
{ numb : 10,
question:"An individual computer connected to a central computer and to other computers on a network is a:",
answer:"Workstation",
options:[
"Workstation",
"Netbook",
"Terminal",
"Nodes"
]
},
];